Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences records, 1907-2004 RG0010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Columbian College of Arts and Sciences Graduate Studies Office records
1907-2004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences. Office of the Dean
RG0010
22.75 Linear Feet
This collection includes annual reports, statistics, correspondence, memos, dean's files, department and program files, dissertation lists, meeting minutes, and brochures.
Bib #
Conditions Governing Access
Some material may be copyrighted or restricted. It is the patron's obligation to determine and satisfy copyright or other case restrictions when publishing or otherwise distributing materials found in the collections.
Washington (D.C.); Doctor of philosophy degree -- United States; Dissertations, Academic; Scholarships; Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Courses and lectures; Seminars; Salamon, Linda Bradley; Solomon, Henry; Kenny, Robert; Lefton, Lester A.; George Washington University. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences; George Washington University; Burns, Arthur Edward; George Washington University. Columbian College of Arts and Sciences; Frawley, William
- Departmental files, 1913-2004; RG0010 Series 1; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains pamphlets, correspondence, memorandums, brochures, newsletters, application packets, proposal, by-laws, press releases, posters, and handbooks. They range in date from 1913 to 2004. The materials concern the style for George Washington University's theses and dissertations for master's students; courses; requirements; deans; admission information; the Radiological Sciences program; faculty by-laws; fellowships; scholarships; graduate assistantships; enrollment; "The Virtual Trail: political journalism on the Internet"; the Institute for Politics, Democracy & the Internet; the Graduate School of Political Management; degree programs; off-campus programs; student handbooks; a Graduate Student in Genetics handbook; the School of Media and Public Affairs's Journalism Department; the Political Science Department; the Sociology Department; the Robert A. Taft Institute of Government Seminars; awards and prizes; and the Columbian College of Arts and Science.
  - Awards & Prizes, 1969 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences (1967- ), 12/06/1977 --1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Admissions, 02/1973 -2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Advanced Degree Program In Radiological Sciences, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Applicants For Graduation, 04/04/1974 --09/30/1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Faculty By-Laws, 01/28/1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Fellowship Information Center (1967-1982), 03/01/1967 --08/16/1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Graduate Enrollment, 1992-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences - Graduate School of Political Management, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Masters Programs, 1997 -2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Off-Campus Programs, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Off-Campus Programs Brochures, 1972-06/1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences-- Student Handbook, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences-- Student Handbook, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences-- Student Handbook, 1979-2000, 1979-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School Of Arts And Sciences--Thesis And Dissertation Style Information, 1960 --04/02/2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Journalism Department, 1948 --09/26/1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Political Science Department, 06/1913 --01/1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Political Science Department Robert A. Taft Institute of Government Seminars, 1977-1980, 04/01/1976 --07/1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sociology Department, 1929-1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Theses and dissertations - information concerning theses and dissertations, 01/1973 --01/1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Annual reports, Ph.D. statistics, and daily life files, 1907-1977; RG0010 Series 2; 3 Linear Feet 2 record center cartons (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series contains annual reports and Ph.D. statistics from 1907-1967, and "daily life files" from 1972-1977. The daily life files are chronolgoical files of memoranda and correspondence produced by the office of Henry Solomon, dean of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, except for the daily life files labled "Manpower." These are chronological files of correspondence and reports related to the Econometric Research on Navy Manpower Problems program.
  - Doctorate Disputations, 1907-1918 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Council, 1931-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - List of Theses Written by Candidates Whose Degrees Granted from 2/22/32 to 1941, 1932-1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Selections from Minutes of the Graduate Council, 10/1931 --12/1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Council, 1939-1950 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ph. D. Graduates by Field Since 1950, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ph. D. Graduates in English, 1950-1967 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Spring 1967 Ph. D. Figures by Department (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Fall 1966 Ph. D. Figures by Department (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Council - Old Registration Figures, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Ph. D. Admissions Statistics, Graduate Council, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Ph. D. Statistics, Graduate Council, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Annual Report, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Annual Report, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Annual Report, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - The Graduate Council, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Graduate Council, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Daily Life File -- Manpower, 04/1972 --12/1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Daily Life File -- Manpower, 05/1973 --07/1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Daily Life File -- Manpower, 08/1973 --12/1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Daily Life File -- Manpower, 01/1974 --12/1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Daily Life File, 01/1975 --04/1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Daily Life File, 05/1975 --09/1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Daily Life File -- Manpower, 01/1975 --12/1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Daily Life File, 03/1976 --06/1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Daily Life File, 12/1976 --04/1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Daily Life File, 01/1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Daily Life File, 05/1977 --08/1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Daily Life File, 09/1977 --12/1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Minutes of the Graduate Council, dissertation lists, and course brochures, 1939-1957; RG0010 Series 3; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains minutes of the Graduate Council, dissertation lists, and course brochures, in addition to a paper on Bearcreek, Montana coal mining. They range in date from 1939-57.
  - Gerontology Program Curriculum, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of Graduate Council, 11/07/1952 --04/27/1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of Graduate Council, 03/16/1943 --04/26/1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes of Graduate Council, 03/15/1939 --07/14/1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Doctoral Dissertations (vol. 1-11), undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mihous and Hume: Eight English Plays 1675-1707, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Graduate department brochures, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Paper: Bearcreek, Montana: An Interdisciplinary Photographic and Historical Study of a Coal Mining Community with Evaluations of Research Methods, by Virginia Heidenreich, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Departmental files, 1943-1988; RG0010 Series 4; 6 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series contains dean's departmental files for American Studies, Art Therapy, Chemistry, Biochemistry, Center for Washington Area Studies, Corcoran Hall renovation, Classics, History, German, Women's Studies, School of Education, School of Medicine, School of Engineering, School of Government, International Student Services, and prizes and awards. They range in date from 1943-88.
  - Administrative Sc. Program, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Red Cross Program, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Studies, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Avery Andrews Chron Files [1/2], 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Avery Andrews Chron Files [2/2], 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Antrhopology [1/2], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Antrhopology [2/2], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Armed Forces Institute, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Art Department, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anatomy Dept, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Art Therapy Faculty, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Biochemistry, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Biological Sciences, 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Edward Caress Chron. Files [1/8], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Edward Caress Chron. Files [2/8], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Edward Caress Chron. Files [3/8], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Edward Caress Chron. Files [4/8], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Edward Caress Chron. Files [5/8], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Edward Caress Chron. Files [6/8], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Edward Caress Chron. Files [7/8], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Edward Caress Chron. Files [8/8], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry [1/3], 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chemistry [2/3], 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chemistry [3/3], 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Campaign for GW [1/2], 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Campaign for GW [2/2], 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Center for Washington Area Studies, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Consortium Army Research, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Conflict of Interest Cmte, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - CORCORAN HALL RENOVATION, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Continuing Education [1/2], 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Continuing Education [2/2], 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Consortium Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Council of Dean, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Council of Graduate School BiSc Dissertaion Awds, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Council on Doctoral Programs [1/3], 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Council on Doctoral Programs [2/3], 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Council on Doctoral Programs [3/3], 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Council on International Programs, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Classics [1/2], 1970-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Classics [2/2], 1970-1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Commencement, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Patent & Procedures [1/2], 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Patent & Procedures [2/2], 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Resource Policy, 1972-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - History, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Latin American Studies, 1959-1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Math / Math Lab., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Naval ROTC, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Language Lab, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Speech and Hearing, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Women's Studies, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Council of Graduate School - Tax Code Changes, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Council of Graduate School, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - German, 1980-1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - School of Education and Human Development, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - School of Medicine and Health Servcies, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fellowship office, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CONSORTIUM, 1964-1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING AND APPLIED SCIENCES, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - News and Public Affairs, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Gelman Library, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Internaitonal Student SErvices, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - DEAN OF STUDENTS, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - School of Government and Business Administration, 1971-1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Summer Advance Registration Program, 1970-1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Report to Board of Trustees, 10/1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Accredidation Visit, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Prizes and Awards, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Prizes, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma: Botany, 1943-1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Alpha Chi Sigma: Chemistry, 1952-1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Astiere Claeyssens Prize - English, 1972-1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Alice Gouglas Goddard, 1952-1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bysne Thurrell Burns Memorial, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Willie E. Fitch - Chemistry, 1960-1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bejamin Van Evera - Chem. Society of Washington, 1972-1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Chemical Rubber Company Award - Chemistry, 1965-1986 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - DeWitt Clinton Croissant, 1952-1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - E.K. Cutter Prize, 1951-1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Prizes and Awards, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Prizes and Awards, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Prizes and Awards, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Art Faculty Awards, 1972-1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Art - David Lloyd Kreeger, 1970-1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Botany - Kappa Kappa Gamma Prize, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Chemistry - American Chem Society Prize, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Chemistry - American Institute of Chemistry PRize, 1951-1986 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Chemistry - Alpha Chi Sigma, 1952-1986 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chemistry - Chemical Rubber Company Award, 1965-1986 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chemistry - Benjamin Van Evera / Chem. Soceity of Washington, 1972-1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chemistry - Willie E. Fitch Prize, 1960-1984 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Chemistry - Byrne Thurtell Burns Memorial Prize, 1951-1986 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - English - Alice Douglas Goddard Prize, 1952-1986 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - English - Astere Claeyssens Prize, 1972-1986 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - English - De Witt Clinton Croissant Prize, 1952-1984 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - English - Vivian Nellis Memorial Award, 1966-1985 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - History - Thomas F. Walsh, 1926-1983 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - History - Elmer Louis Kayser Prize in History, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - History - Jessie Fant Evans Award in Contemporary History, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - History - Charles C. Swisher Historical Club, 1951-1985 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - History - Gardiner G. Hubbard, American History, 1951-1986 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Journalism - Jesse Frederick Essay Prize, 1951-1986 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Speech and Drama - Isaac Davis Public Speaking Prize, 1951-1985 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Classics - Elton Prize in Greek, 1950-1986 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Clasiscs - John Francis Latimer Prize in Classics, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Germanic Languages & Literature - Hermann & Johanna Richter Schoenfeld, 1967-1986 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Classics, 1942-1985 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Mathematics - Ruggles Prize, 1952-1986 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Mathematics - James H. Taylor Graduate Math. Prize, 1976-1986 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Music - Barry Manilow Prize, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Philosophy - Charles E. Gauss Prize, 1977-1986 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Rom. Languages & Lit. - Edward Carrington Goddard Prize, 1952-1986 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Rom. Languages & Lit. - Henry Grattan Doyle Award, 1966-1986 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Political Sc. - Joshua Evans Prize in Polit. Sc. & Social Sc., 1951-1984 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Physics - James MacBride Sterrett, Jr. Prize, 1950-1986 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Phsychology - Psi Chi Prize, 1951-1986 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Sociology - Hilda Manchester Prize, 1972-1986 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Statistics - Minna Mirin Kullback Memorial Prize, 1969-1986 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Phi Eta Sigma, 1962-1985 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Political Science - Alexander Wilbourne Weddell Peace Essay Prize, 1926-1986 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Departmental files, 1931-1987; RG0010 Series 5; 12 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 5, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series contains records of Dean Robert Bolwell, Dean Henry Solomon, Dean's Council, experimental programs, Academic Center planning, and various departments. They range in date from 1931-87.
  - Academic Cluster Planning, 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Academic Center building
  - Academic Program Evaluation, Columbia College, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Dishonesty, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Admissions Office, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Sciences, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - African American Institute, 1968 -1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Council on Education, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Studies/Library of Congress, 1972 -1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Studies Program, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American University: GWU Exchange Agreement, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anatomy Department, 1965-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Andrews, Avery D., 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Chronology
  - Andrews, Avery D., 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Anthropology Department, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Appeal Procedures, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Armed Forces Institute of Pathology, 1972-1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Art Department, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Art Therapy Program, 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Biological Sciences Department, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Biochemistry, 1971-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Biomedical Sciences, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bolwell, Robert: Chair, Graduate School, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Burns, Arthur, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Caress, Edward, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Caress, Edward, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cartography Program, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Proposed
  - Caws, Peter, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Chemical Toxicology, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Chemistry Department, 1970-1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Clinical Engineering and Medical, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Physics Ph.D. Proposal College of General Studies, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Collegium for Humanistic Study, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences Committee on Patent Policy and Procedure, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Communication and Theatre, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Committee on the Communications and Performing Arts, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Consortium: Academic Planning Project, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Consortium: Army Research Institute, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Consortium: Army Research Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Consortium of Universities Academic, 06/1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Planning Report Consortium Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Consortium: East Asian Art History Proposal, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Consortium: Meeting Minutes, 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Continuing Education, Division of, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Council of Deans, 1971-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Council of Graduate Schools Masters, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Education Project Creative Writing MFA Program Proposal, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Criminal Justice Program, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cunliff, Marcus, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Deans' Council, 1967-1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Deans' Council, 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Development Office, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dilthey Faculty Fellowships, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dimock Gallery, 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Doctoral Dissertation Procedures, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Doctoral Program Committees, 1967-1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Economics Department, 1978-1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Economics Development Plan, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Economics Development Plan, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Education and Human Development, School of, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Education Policy Program, 1973-1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Education Policy Program Ad Hoc Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Energy Resource Policy Program, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, School of, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - English Department, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - English for International Students, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Environmental Science Program, 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Environmental and Resource Policy, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Epidemiology and Environmental Health, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1971-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Experimental Program, Division of, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Experimental Program, Division of, 1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Faculty Publications
  - Experimental Programs Steering Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    General File
  - Experimental Programs Steering Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Experimental Programs Steering Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Experimental Programs Steering Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Exxon Education Foundation Grant, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Exxon-Sloan Foundation Grant, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Code: Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Fellowship Information Center, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Service Institute, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Forensic Science Department, 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - General Accounting Office, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Genetics Program, 1969-1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Genetics Faculty Appointments, 1969-1983 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Geobiology Program, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Geography, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Geology Department, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Geology Department, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Geriatrics/Gerontology Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Gerontology Graduate Program, 1978-1983 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Archival materials
  - Gerontology Program, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Government and Business Administration, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - School of Graduate Council Minutes, 1931-1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Council Minutes, 1957-1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Student Research Day, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Codification Rules, Regs, Procedures, 1960-1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Comprehensive Report, 07/1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Faculty Meeting Agendas, 1967-1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Faculty Meeting Agendas, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)